# SHREYANSH **RAVAL**

WEB DEVELOPER





+91 7226831663



raval201081@gmail.com



n Dehgam

# Education

#### **BCA**

Silver Oak University 2021 - 2024 9.18 CGPA

#### **HSC**

Revaba Vidhyamandir 2020 - 2021 70.28%

## SSC

Revaba Vidhyamandir 2018 - 2019 72.67%

# Language

**English** 

Gujarati

Hindi

## About me

I am a Web Developer with nearly one year of experience in building responsive websites. I am passionate about learning and improving my skills, and I enjoy collaborating with teams to solve problems and create userfriendly solutions. I am eager to grow professionally and contribute to new and exciting projects.

# **Experience**

### Junior Web Developer

July 2024 - Present

eBranding Studio

#### Technical Support Intern

Nov 2022 - May 2023

Sunshine Info Solution

## Skills

## **Frontend Development Tools**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap

## **Tools**

Git, GitHub, Visual Studio Code, Chrome DevTools

#### **Techniques**

Responsive Design, Cross-browser Compatibility, Web Performance Optimization

#### **CMS**

WordPress (Theme Customization, Plugins, Content Management)

#### **Technical SEO**

Website Structure Optimization Page Speed Optimization Mobile Optimization